Joy
Jagannath, today I will discuss some important topics about
insurance, vehicle
insurance, what are the
most important tips, what are the
points that are important, you
need to know these things at the time of claim, I have
said that it can be a bike
or a car, it can be a CB bike, I will not talk about
accidents, I will not talk about accidents, any
momentary accidents can come in life, there are
different types of accidents, if you
go, whether it is an accident during the day, whether the
car is broken,
whether your house is locked or where you park your car, whether the house is broken, if the
car is broken, if the
car is damaged,
if there is insurance, how much will I
claim for it, the main
content of today is this video, you will learn a lot,
without skipping, I will know that how much
I
Can I get my compensation in the proper way? This is an
important thing. First, you know that
if you buy your car, then you do not have
insurance from any company.
According to the IDI rule ID report, there are 58
insurance companies in India.
Out of which 24 companies are life
insurance
companies and 34 are general insurance
companies. There are 34 general insurance
companies. If you have a bike, various
types of products, except for life, then all the remaining
general
insurance will be covered under it.
If you do
not have a seat in any of these 34 insurance companies, then you have
nothing to worry about. If you
face an accident, if an accident happens, then you should
first give importance to your own
safety, first give importance to your own and third party
safety, if anything happens, then
Think about medication, fast
treatment,
call an ambulance or fire brigade,
call people, arrange for your immediate tank to be sent
and
treat yourself, if any injury occurs,
this is your first duty and keep your
bike in such a place that there is
no accident again
or people will not have any problems, right,
after the accident, it is your
duty to take all the angles, you know, there is
no video footage, you know, photocopy
some protection from different
angles, which is what we will get proof from at the time of claim settlement,
if some people have submitted, keep
some eye witnesses
in the statement,
put the number in the number, tell them,
it is practically a case of various types of cases, whether it is
small things or not,
but those points are the same.  I will go to pay it off so
that I can claim a lot of money
and if necessary, I will be in the middle of rejection.
The claim will not be rejected
and you will get your money back properly. You will get
compensation for the damage to the city.
That is the important thing. Okay,
step one. If I see any fast safety,
then I will take my photo or
video footage and if there is any witness, if there is any
document, baby, if you face any problem in an unknown place, then you will
know your footage and photo and inform the police fast.
If you have been injured, I know which local police
station you are, grandson. You have nothing to worry about.
Dial your police helpline 100. The nearest police station will be
contacted. Inform your metro relations.
And if there are more injuries,
dial the number of your fire station.
Can you help me? And the reporter will
visit the police station. What will you do if you are more injured?  The spot is okay. The
second thing is to check your vehicle first. Whether the
car is in moving condition or
not. Whether the running condition is suitable or not.
If there is a petrol leak,
any seat is damaged, the wheel is
broken, the car is registered in the condition of the car. If you do not know where to look,
you will take care of the car. If you are moving,
go to the nearest police station,
report it first. Report the FIR to the
police. And during that
time, if you
buy a car from an insurance company, if you buy it from an
insurance company, if you buy it from a
bike showroom or if you buy it from a bike showroom,
General insurance
means if you have to do it,
inform me about it and
tell me about the meter thoroughly. The
important thing is that the
report should be equal between your FIR report and the
words you said
and you should speak honestly and truthfully. There should be no
cheating or cheating. If
it is not a matter of fact,
I am currently practicing on the genuine problem that people are facing. Your
date, time, where you
went on the road will be very important and the
location is the main thing. The location is the
time, date, this is the reason for the accident. Whether you
were right or not, what else is there, what has been
added, what is the incident, it will be
reported in the
affair report and
inform your insurance agent.
If there is no agent, call your showroom
or your  The insurance paper that is there is
that customer care of your
insurance
company, you can dial the toll free number of
your meter, you can see the total technique of the
toll free number of
your paper online, you can
open the website available to you, you can see it or
nowadays different companies are looking at it in the mobile app, you can
register your complaint online through that app, you
can do the step two, I will
give you what I give you, if I give the information to the police
and the company, I mean the company,
I will inform the complaint, then the third
step is I will try my car or if I can get
my car to the garage, your
insurance advisor or
customer care will inform you, if there is a garage in the area, if there is a garage in the area, then
make arrangements for that garage, or consult with the network that
I am very far from the network of the
network garage  I will
work at your station, how can I do that? I will
suggest you, I will
do it according to your suggestion. Okay, after reaching the garage, may
Allah bless you, then I will think about some things. In that case, I will
know how my
claim is.
What documents are required at the time of this claim? I
need to know the documents required at the time of my claim.
It is fast. Your policy copy. Next is the
registration certificate of the RC vehicle
and your DL. The documents that own the car. And
if you are a driver, you will
give your DL. Important things
mean that during the campaign, you will think about whether you were
wearing a seat belt or
not. In this matter, you will pay attention to whether you are wearing a
seat belt.
Remember this important point. If you are
driving without a seat belt,
many problems can arise in your claim. So
always watch your safety
and drive safely.  If you are not
wearing a seat belt, then I will put it in your PAN card and
Aadhaar card. You will apply
with your email address and phone number.
Okay, the garage will give
you a fast estimate in the garage. I
suggest a network garage or your own garage. The company that
reaches it
will estimate all the damage that you have done.
After leaving, the entire
estimate bill will be sent to your insurance
department.
After leaving, the company
will assess your area and
send an agent to the car. What kind of survey will it take? Who will do the survey? He will come to you and survey
your car. What
damage has actually happened to your car?
Which parts are broken? He will
check the technical aspects and check it. God willing,
after going to the office, they will prepare a
list and the company will mail it
or let you know.  The role is very
important
in this, when you get your claim, the insurance visitor who will come to you
as a visitor, that
I will move it, that role is
very important, okay, then tell everything
as clean and tell everything honestly, with
all the documents, as if you
can get the claim,
then tell him to go and get the car
repaired, he will say that it will be repaired, it will be
ready, then the estimate bill will be released,
then the tax invoice will be made, then the
tax invoice will be made, then the
reserve money will come, he will see
that whatever
damage has been done, whether it has been properly applied, whether the
car is completely
addressed, whether there is a denting policy, whether there is any part
exchange, whether it is
properly repaired, if everything was 100% right, then you
can pay it directly or your payment will be made to
your company.  I am in two situations, whether I will make the
payment myself or the company will pay
you later. I will
deal with your insurance advisor and talk to him and do the work. I
mean, I know the whole thing that
I do insurance. There are different
types of insurance, which are first
party, second party, third party. I will
bring you detailed videos of these works. Please
subscribe to your channel. If you like
the video, like it. There are many things to say.
Listen to the zero depreciation. There are
two things in first party insurance,
which are zero depreciation and
comprehensive zero depreciation. If
your insurance covers it,
then I will give the total coverage company and
how will I give it? The tax invoice will go. You will
repair it yourself. God willing, the garage will get the
amount
and the tax liability amount.
Where will you get the liability amount?  Let's take an
example, you have a
bill of three lakh taka
for your car damage,
but you have to pay three lakh taka for your liability amount.
Some
parts that the company has not given,
some plastic materials, some
materials that have a description, they will
not give them to you. If they are not given,
you will pay only the
liability amount that
you decide according to your IDB value, IDB
value with NCB, etc. I will
bring a detailed video in all of the above. If I miss some points,
whatever comes to your attention, I will
write in the comment box. I know that Allah will
cover everything for you. Everything is fine. So if you
mean zero depreciation insurance,
you will get total coverage, but you will get the
liability amount. The rest is the
tax invoice, the rest is your garage.  You will have to
pay the cost if the
comprehensive is 50-50, so that the
company will pay 50% of the parts, you will pay
50%, and
you will have to bear the cost of painting labor, which is 12.5%, and you will have to bear the cost of
compulsory assessment fee,
which is compulsory assessment fee. If you
get any documentation, the company will
inform you about these things. If the
cost of your car is within 10 lakh taka, then how much will the
company charge? But
overall, I have said that out of 15 thousand, 1500 taka is its
fee. If the car is above 10 lakh taka,
then 2000-2500 taka is the fee. There are other
things, see what your damage is
or what damage has been done. Make your claim. Do
not make unnecessary small claims.
So, in the meantime, what is that in your next
insurance period?  NCB said
I can get his bonus if you claim it. Suppose
you have 2000 rupees and small
dents. Minor defects have
become crores. Total trouble if you have eight to ten thousand
rupees. Claim it. There is no
benefit. Do you need to pay your own trouble and
fix the car?
If you claim it, then
you have 20% rebate. It is NCB's 20%
bonus rebate. At that time, if you want to
go for next insurance, your
insurance premium will be
20% less. This is the above.
Bring a detailed video. Okay.
And I have done it again. If you
drive safely, your life is very valuable and
whoever will be in harm's way, please help me. Bring a
video next. How to claim third party insurance? Many people have
insurance. What is very confusing every day
if you claim above.  If there is a death case, how much
money will the
company recover from the Metro's writer? If there is a MSCD case, which is
deleted, bring your next video
today. Jai Jagannath